请进
Come in.
我等你很久了
I've been waiting for you.
嗨  我只是...
Hi, I just...
天啊
My God!
天啊  莫妮卡
Oh, my God! Monica!
天啊
Oh, my God!
抱歉  我
I'm sorry! I was...
我正在睡午觉
I was taking a nap.
你从何时开始用那种怪姿势睡觉
Since when do you take naps in that position?
天啊  莫妮卡  告诉我你是在等男人吧
God, Monica, tell me you were waiting for a guy.
拜托你告诉我你是在等男人
Please tell me you were waiting for a guy.
没错  我在等男人
Yes, I was. A guy.
餐馆同事
From work.
我在跟餐馆同事约会
I'm seeing a guy from work!
你餐馆的那个帅气服务员
That cute waiter guy from you restaurant
长得像亲切版雷·利奥塔的那个吗
that one looks like a nonthreatening Ray Liotta?
就是他
That one!
给我点时间  我马上就闪人
You know what, just give me a second. I'll be out of your hair.
我只需要拿件外套
I'm just gonna grab a jacket.
等我回来后  可要告诉我详情
When I get back, I want every little detail.
他可能来了
Maybe that's him.
好的  好的
Okay... Okay...
只是乔伊跟罗斯
It's just Joey and Ross.
你们不是去看电影吗
Why aren't you at the movie?
对啊  可是罗斯讲电话太吵
We were. But Ross was talk so loud on his phone,
我们被轰出来了
they threw us out.
电影太吵  我当然得大声讲了
I had to talk loud because the movie was loud!
他打电话去伦敦
He's talking to London.
天哪  他和艾蜜莉联系上了吗
My god, did he get in touch with Emily?
还没  但是他打给所有的女方亲戚
No, not yet. He's called everyone on her side of the family,
希望有人愿意帮他联系上她
hoping that someone will help him get in touch with her.
就算我说错名字又如何
I don't care if I said some other girl's name,
你这大惊小怪的笨蛋
you prissy old twit!
罗斯  你巴结亲家真有一套
Ross, way to suck up to the family!
真高兴大家都在
I'm so glad you guys are all here.
我们公司终于买免皱传真纸了
My office finally got wrinkle-free fax paper!
别过来  呕吐礼服  呕吐礼服
No, no! Vomit tux! No, no! Vomit tux!
放心  我送去干洗过了
Don't worry, I had it dry-cleaned.
呕吐礼服
Vomit tux?
谁会吐在礼服上
Who vomited on...?
乔伊  怎么打扮得这么隆重
You know what? What you up to, Joe?
有个电视募捐节目
They're doing this telethon thing on TV.
我的经纪人帮我争取到了嘉宾主持人的活
And my agent got me a job as cohost!
太棒了
That's great!
帮公共广播公司做好事  又能增加曝光率
A little good deed for PBS, plus some TV exposure.
我乔伊最爱做这种事了
That's the kind of math Joey likes to do.
公共广播公司
Oh, PBS!
-他们哪里不对了  -他们哪里对
- What's wrong with PBS? - What's right with them?
你为何不喜欢公共广播公司  菲比
Why don't you like PBS, Pheebs?
因为我妈自杀之后
Right after my Mom killed herself,
我一个人非常难过
I was in a bad place, you know, personally.
所以我想写信给芝麻街
I just thought it'll make me feel better
心情应该会好一点
if I'd write to Sesame Street-
因为我小时候总觉得他们很亲切
'cause they were so nice when I was a little kid.
结果根本没人回信
No one ever wrote back.
你要知道那些布偶没有大拇指
You know a lot of those muppets don't have thumbs.
我只收到一个烂钥匙扣
All I got was a lousy key chain,
拜托  我那时住在纸箱里耶
and by that time, I was living in a box.
连钥匙都没有
I didn't have keys!
我很遗憾  菲比
I'm sorry, Pheebs.
我只是想做好事  就像你帮你弟弟生小孩
I just wanted to do a good deed, like you did with the babies.
你才不是做好事
This isn't a good deed.
你只是想上电视  根本就很自私
You just want to get on TV. This is totally selfish.
你帮你弟弟生小孩又怎么说
What about you having those babies for your brother?
自私的不是只有我
Talking about selfish!
你胡说什么
What are you talking about?
你的确是帮了他们
It was a really nice thing,
不过你自己心情也很好吧
but it made you feel good, right?
那又如何
Yeah, so?
让自己心情好的好事  就算是一种自私
It made you feel good so that makes it selfish.
世界上根本就没有无私的好事  太遗憾了
Look, there's no unselfish good deeds. Sorry.
有的  有很多行善的人都没有私心
Yes, there are. there are totally good deeds that are selfless!
你能举出个例子来吗
May I ask for one example?
当然有  例如
Yeah, it's... You know, there's...
不  我不给你举例
No, you may not!
因为所有人都是自私的
Because all people are selfish.
你说我自私吗
Are you calling me selfish?
你难道不是人吗
Are you calling you people?
菲比  很抱歉戳破你的美梦
Sorry to burst that bubble, Pheebs,
但世界上没有无私的善事
but selfless good deeds don't exist, okay?
你也知道圣诞老人的那套把戏吧
You know the deal on Santa Claus, right?
我一定会找到一件无私的善事
I'm gonna find a selfless good deed.
打败你这个邪恶博士
I'm gonna beat you, you evil genius!
-喂  -喂  罗斯
- Hello. - Hello, Ross.
艾蜜莉
Emily.
天啊  是艾蜜莉
Oh, my God! It's Emily!
大家不要吵
It's Emily, everyone!
嗨
Hi.
罗斯  我只是要告诉你
Ross, I'm only ringing to say
别再骚扰我的亲戚了  再见
stop harassing my relatives. Goodbye.
等等  好吧  你挂吧
No, wait. Okay, you can hang up,
但我会继续打电话
but I'm gonna keep calling,
我会打给所有的英国人
I'm gonna call everyone in England...
如果这样能让你和我讲话  我会打的
...if that's what it takes to get you to talk to me.
是吗  你想谈什么
Really? About what?
你是我的妻子  我们结婚了
Look, you're my wife. We're married.
而且我爱你
You know, I love you.
我很想你
I really miss you!
我也很想你
I miss you too.
至少我认为如此
At least, I think I do-
她肯跟我说话了
She's talking.
乔伊  你刚刚说
Joey, when you said
"圣诞老人的那套把戏"是什么意思
"the deal with Santa," you meant...?
根本没有这号人物
That he doesn't exist.
这样啊
Right.
钱德勒  你听说莫妮卡的地下情人了吗
Chandler, have you heard about Monica's secret boyfriend?
知道  她...她是提过
Yeah, she might have mentioned him.
莫妮卡  我们何时才能认识这个新的
So, Mon, when are we gonna meet this new,
服务生地下情人
secret waiter man?
他很害羞
He's really shy,
我想他现在还没准备好和大家见面
I don't think he's up to meeting everyone yet.
我想他还没准备好
Yeah, I don't think he's up to meeting everyone yet.
我不管
I don't care..
我想见他  她说这家伙在床上一级棒
I want to meet this guy who's the best sex she ever had.
真的
Really?
你听过这话  你说过这话
That's what you heard? You said that?
大概吧
I might have said that.
这有什么好笑
Why is that funny?
因为我很为他高兴
Because I'm very happy for him.
还有你  你真是走狗屎运了
And you! You lucky dog!
艾蜜莉愿意跟我复合
Emily's willing to work on the relationship.
太好了
That's great!
-在伦敦  -什么
- In London. - What?
她要我搬到伦敦去
She wants me to move to London.
可是你住在这里
But you live here.
我这是废话
You know that.
你打算怎么办
What you gonna do?
我打赌如果我跟卡罗尔以及苏珊谈谈
I bet if I talked to Carol and Susan...
一定能说服她们带着本搬到伦敦
...I could convince them to move to London with Ben.
我想你前妻一定
I'm sure your ex-wife would be
非常乐意搬到国外
more than happy to move to another country,
帮你挽回新太太
...so you can patch things up with your new wife.
不是不可能啊
It could happen.
你好  欢迎  幸会
How you doing? Welcome. Good to see you.
这就是你的电话
This'll be your phone.
真好  但是
That's great, but...
应该没有人会打来找我
I'm not really expecting a lot of calls.
你负责接电话接受捐款
No, you answer it and take pledges.
可我是主持人
But I'm the host.
盖瑞·卡林才是主持人  你负责接电话
No, Gary Collins is the host. You'll be answering the phone.
你看起来还不明白
You don't seem to understand.
我以前可是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray.
你负责这支电话  医生
Well, here's your phone, doctor.
我竟然找不到一件无私的善行
I can't believe I can't find a selfless good deed.
你们知道我家隔壁那个老头吧
You know that old guy that lives next door to me?
我偷溜到他家  帮他打扫前廊的落叶
I snuck over there and raked up the leaves on his front stoop.
他捉到我之后  强迫我喝饮料吃饼干
But he caught me, and he force-fed me cider and cookies.
可是我却很开心  那个老混蛋
Then I felt wonderful. That old jackass!
或许乔伊说得对
Maybe Joey's right.
所有好事的出发点都有私心
Maybe all good deeds are selfish.
我一定要找到一件无私的善行
I will find a selfless good deed.
毕竟我才刚生出三个宝宝
I just gave birth to three children...
不能让他们在乔伊有理的世界里长大
...and I won't let them be raised in a world where Joey's right!
莫妮卡
Monica,
-可以问你有关烹饪的问题吗  -当然
- Can I ask you a cooking question? - Sure.
如果你在炉子上烹饪
If you're cooking on the stove...
是否代表你的新地下情人
...that means your new secret boyfriend
在床上比理查德还厉害
is better in bed than Richard?
钱德勒
Chandler!
有吗
Is he?
我要尊重秘密新男友的隐私
I think I'm going to respect the privacy of my new, secret boyfriend.
为什么
Why?
如果我是他
If this guy was me...
又知道自己
...and it's me who'd learned that
是你碰到过的最棒的情人
it was me who was the best you'd ever had...
我一定乐歪了
...I'd be like this:
艾蜜莉
All right, Emily.
虽然我很爱你
As much as I love you...
抱歉  但我不能丢下本去伦敦
...l'm sorry, I can't move to London without Ben.
我知道这很为难你
I understand that would be difficult.
请你考虑下搬过来好吗
Would you please consider moving here?
你本来就打算搬来
I mean you were moving here anyway.
为何不现在就来呢
Why can't you just do that?
我不知道  只是
I don't know. It's just...
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
我知道自己到目前为止的表现
But I know that even though I've been
都是彻头彻尾的白痴
a complete idiot up till now...
但你还是应该过来
...you have to come here.
你必须来  这样我们才能继续走下去
You have to, so we can work this out together-
好吧
All right.
"好吧"  你刚说"好"吗
"All right"? Did you just say "all right"?
没错  现在换我是白痴了
I did. Now I'm the idiot.
艾蜜莉  太棒了
Emily, that is so great!
太棒了
It's gonna be so great!
我们就像坠入爱河的白痴
We're gonna be like two idiots in love!
罗斯  有件事还是让我很担心
Ross, there's one thing that really scares me still.
-你尽管说  -你要知道
- Yes, tell me. - You have to understand...
婚礼那天我有多丢脸
...how humiliating it was for me at the altar...
在我的亲朋好友面前
...in front of my family and all friends.
我知道  我非常抱歉
I know. I am so sorry.
然后  当我决定原谅你
And then, after deciding to forgive you...
却在机场  看到你跟她赶着上飞机
...seeing you at the airport, catching our plane with her.
这也是我的错
Again, very sorry.
我是说我根本无法与她共处一室
I mean, I can't be in the same room as her.
我光想到你跟她共处一室就快气坏了
It drives me mad just thinking of you being in the same room as her.
艾蜜莉  我跟瑞秋根本没什么
Emily, there is nothing between Rachel and me.
好吗
Okay?
我爱的是你
I love you.
好吧
All right.
我去纽约  我们再试试看
I'll come to New York, and we'll try to make this work.
太好了
That's so great!
只要你答应不再见瑞秋
As long as you don't see Rachel anymore.
我就问艾蜜莉愿不愿意来纽约
I asked Emily if she would come to New York.
她答应了
And she said yes.
-太好了  -好棒
- Yes! - Great!
先别激动
No, no, no!
条件是我不准再见瑞秋
Only if I promise never to see Rachel again.
什么  你不可以...
What? You can't...
-你怎么说的  -我说我得考虑下
- What did you tell her? - I told her I have to think about it.
我到底该怎么决定
How the hell am I supposed to make this kind of decision?
我这是在问你们
I'm actually asking you!
你不能从此不见瑞秋
You can't just not see Rachel anymore,
她是你的好朋友
she is one of your best friends.
但他也不能不见艾蜜莉
Yeah. But he can't exactly not see Emily,
-她可是他老婆  -也是
- that's his wife! - That's true!
但是  你跟瑞秋从中学就认识
But, you've known Rachel since high school,
你不能说不见就不见瑞秋了
you can't just cut Rachel out of your life!
-你说得也对  -我也不能不见她
- That's true! - Neither can I.
谢谢你们的帮忙  问题一点也没解决
Thanks for the help. Problem solved!
-喂  -莫妮卡
- Hello. - Hey, Mon.
乔伊
Hey, Joey.
我们看了很久了  你何时才会上电视
we've been watching all day, when will you be on TV?
我经纪人搞错了
See, there was kind of a mix-up in my agent's office...
但我还是上了电视  增加了曝光率
...but I'm still on TV, and that's good exposure.
你没上电视啊
You're not on TV.
好吧  现在呢
Okay. How about now?
看到他了  看到他了
There he is! There he is!
你好  纽约
Hello, New York!
也许只要把整只鸭子放进去  管它呢
Maybe just put the whole duck right in there- Who cares?
我先处理鸭腿
You know, now I got the legs-
我说过多少次
How many times have I told you guys
不准看烹饪频道
never watch the cooking channel?
钱德勒
Hi, Chandler.
我来要回乔伊上次借的烤盘
I need that broiling pan that Joey borrowed the other day.
那是你的吗
That was yours?
我们上次用来盛阿鸭吐出来的虫子
We used it when the duck was throwing up caterpillars.
《威廉索诺玛》秋季刊27页
Williams-Sonoma, fall catalog, page 27.
四到六周后送货到家
Expect it in 4 to 6 weeks.
乔伊今天一整天都不在
Joey's gonna be at the telethon for the rest of the day.
整个家里就只有我们两个
We have the whole place to ourselves.
那又如何
Yeah, so?
我只是想  也许你想和最佳情人
Well I just, thought maybe you'd wanna book some time
预约时间约会
with the best you'd ever had.
你知道吗  最佳情人
You know what, champ?
我打算放弃
I think I'll pass.
为什么
Why?
什么意思
What's your point?
公共广播公司电视募捐
PBS Telethon.
乔伊
Hey, Joey.
我只是想告诉你  我找到无私的善行了
I just wanted to let you know that I found a selfless good deed.
我刚去公园让蜜蜂螫我
I went down to the park and I let a bee sting me.
什么  这对谁有好处
What? What good is that gonna do anybody?
这只蜜蜂在同伴面前会脸上有光
Well, it helps the bee look tough in front of his bee friends.
蜜蜂很开心  我却很痛
The bee is happy, and I am definitely not.
你知道吗  蜜蜂螫完你可能就会死了
You know, the bee probably died after he stung you.
可恶
Damn it!
各位  三十秒后开始录影
Back on in 30 seconds, people!
抱歉  可以跟你换位子吗
Excuse me, would you mind switching with me?
甭想  我刚好在镜头里
No way. I'm in the shot, man.
-你已经占这位子一天了  -我在接受捐款
- Come on, you've been here all day! - I'm taking pledges.
倒数计时三  二...
And we're on three, two...
欢迎继续收看秋季电视募捐
Welcome back to our fall telethon.
如果各位喜欢"太阳马戏团"的表演
If you've been enjoying the performance Cirque du Soleil...
以后还想收看
...and you'd like to see more
同类型节目  方法很简单
the same kind of programme, it's very simple.
只要打电话捐款
All you have to do is call in a pledge...
并告诉我们的义工接线员
and at that time tell operator one of our volunteers
喜欢收看哪类节目
what type of programming you...
好了  够了
Okay. That's it.
我无法做决定  这实在太难了
I cannot make this decision. It is too difficult.
我决定全权交给命运之神
So I'm gonna just leave it entirely up to the gods of fate.
神奇八号球
A Magic 8 Ball?
你怎么可以用玩具决定命运
You can't be serious. You can't make this decision with a toy!
这可不是玩具
It's not a toy.
我别无选择
I don't know what else to do!
不是追回老婆  失去好朋友
I mean I either keep my wife and lose one of my best friends...
就是留下朋友
...or I keep my friend,
在三十岁前离婚两次
get divorced for the second time before I'm 30.
要是有人有更好的建议  现在就说出来
So if anyone else has a better suggestion, let's hear it.
我没别的办法了  大家别害羞
Because I got nothing! Don't be shy.
各种建议都可以
Any suggestion will do.
好吧
Okay, then.
开始了
Here we go.
神奇八号球
Magic 8 Ball...
我是不是不该再见瑞秋
...should I never see Rachel again?
待会再问
"Ask Again Later."
这个答案不够好
Later is not good enough!
待会再问  怎么回事
"Ask Again Later." What the hell?
这东西坏掉了  坏掉了
This is broken! It is broken!
我来看看
Let me see.
钱德勒今晚会跟女人上床吗
Will Chandler have sex tonight?
别太指望
"Don't count on it."
我倒觉得没坏掉
Seems like it works to me.
公共广播公司电视募捐
PBS Telethon.
乔伊
Hi, Joey-
菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
我要捐钱
I'd like to make a pledge.
我想捐两百元
I would like to donate $200.
两百元
Two hundred dollars?
你确定吗  菲比  芝麻街可是伤你不浅
You sure? Pheebs, after what Sesame Street did to you?
我还是很生气  但是我知道
I'm still mad at them, but I also know
很多妈妈没自杀的
they bring happiness to lots of kids
小孩很爱看
whose moms didn't kill themselves.
为了支持这节目
You know, so... By supporting them,
我决定做件好事  不过我自己可不开心
I'm doing a good thing, but I'm not happy about it.
你看  这就是无私的善行
So there! A selfless good deed.
难道你捐钱没有一点开心吗
You don't feel a little good about donating the money?
难过死了  我本想用这笔钱买只仓鼠
No, it sucks! I was saving up to buy a hamster.
仓鼠  那种宠物十元就买得到
A hamster? Those things are, like, $ 10.
我喜欢的那只可没那么便宜
Not the one I had my eye on.
看来今年的捐款已经超过了去年总额
It looks like we have surpassed last year's pledge total.
谢谢各位观众
Thank you viewers!
打破纪录的捐款是由我们这位义工募得
And the pledge that did it was taken by one of our volunteers-
天哪  我得说
Oh, boy! And may I say,
这位穿得可够隆重的
one of our sharpest dressed volunteers-
乔瑟夫·崔比安尼先生
Mr.Joseph Tribbiani!
快看
Oh, look!
乔伊上电视了
Joey's on TV!
太棒了
Isn't that great?
我的捐款让乔伊上了电视
My pledge got Joey on TV!
这真是让我...
That makes me feel so...
糟糕
Oh, no!
听我说
Look...
或许我先前太得意了
Maybe I got carried away before,
不过有件事要告诉你
but there's something you got to know.
如果我表现得很好  也是因为你
If I'm the best, it's only because you made me the best.
说下去
Keep talking.
跟你在一起之前  我根本表现平平
I was nothing before you.
你可以打去问我以前那些女友
Call the other girls and ask.
你一定很快就问完了
Which wouldn't take long.
但是我跟你  我们在一起
But when I'm with you, and we're together...
我的天
...oh, my God!
-真的吗  -我的天
- Really? - Oh, my God!
如果你不想再跟我上床  我也能体谅
Now, I understand if you never want to sleep with me again.
不过这决定是错的
But that would be wrong.
我们太厉害了
We're too good.
不上床实在太可惜
We owe it to sex!
如果真是这样
If we owe it!
天啊
Oh, my!
乔伊何时回来
When is Joey gonna be home?
我们应该不需要等他吧
I was kind of hoping we could do this without him.
没关系  手套不用脱
No, no, no! Leave the gloves on.
可是我刚才在清洁厕所
But I just cleaned the bathroom.
那就脱掉吧
Why don't we lose the gloves.
-好  让大家看看谁才是高手  -好
- All right. Let's show them how it's done. - Okay.
-这不包括在内  -我知道
- You know that wasn't part of it? - I know.
你准备好没  我们要迟到了
Hi. You ready? We're gonna be late.
-迟到什么  -看史黛拉啊  你没忘吧
- For what? - For Stella, remember?
《当老牛碰上嫩草》二十分钟后就开演了
She's getting her groove back in 20 minutes.
我完全忘记了
I totally forgot about that.
你不介意我爽约一次吧
Do you mind I take a rain check?
我正在等艾蜜莉的电话
I'm waiting for a call from Emily.
没关系
Sure, I guess.
听说你不用去伦敦了  太好了
Hey, I hear you don't have to go to London. Yay!
事情没那么简单  我们还有很多问题
It's not that easy. There's still a lot of relationship stuff.
例如
Like what?
就是一些问题
Just stuff.
就是  艾蜜莉对我有些要求
You know, kind of what Emily wants.
你可以告诉我  或许我帮得上忙
Well, why don't you talk to me about it, maybe I can help.
不不  你帮不上忙
No, no. You can't help.
这事我必须自己做决定
I mean, I kind have to do this without your help.
那好吧
Well...
我知道你自己办得到
I know you can do that too.
但是如果你想找人谈谈
I'm just saying if you need somebody to talk...
有我在
Hi!
谢了
Thanks.
罗斯
Ross.
无论艾蜜莉有何要求
Look, whatever this relationship stuff that Emily wants
你答应就是了
...just give it to her.
最重要的是你爱她
The bottom line is that you love her.
她怎么要求  你就怎么做
Just fix whatever she wants fixed.
答应就对了
Just do it.
你总得试试看
I mean you're gonna have to try.
不试试以后一定会后悔
You'll just gonna hate yourself if you don't.
快接电话啊  吵死了
Come on, answer it! It's driving me crazy!
喂  亲爱的
Hello. Hi, sweetie.
我很好  听我说
Good. Look...
我考虑过
Yes, I've been thinking about
你的要求
that thing you wanted me to do, and...
我办得到
I can do it.
你愿意来纽约吗
So will you come to New York?
怎么样
What?
-以前没试过这招  -没
- Never done that before. - Nope.